

Surrey, UK 07935408399

zoepointon123@gmail.com

zoeellenpointon.com



#### ANALYTICS SKILLS

Python

D3

Microsoft Excel

## **UX SKILLS**

User Journeys Prototyping User Testing Focus Groups

#### **DEV SKILLS**

HTML CSS

#### DESIGN SOFTWARE

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign

After Effects XDSketch

Invision Zeplin

Balsamic

# PERSONAL STATEMENT

Currently studying a masters in Design Informatics, at the University of Edinburgh. Two years design experience working within the Tech Industry. Graduated from the University of Winchester with a first class honours in Digital Media Design. Looking for a new opportunity in user experience analysis or data science.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# TruDigital, Portsmouth - UX/UI Designer APR 2018 - JUL 2018

Formerly part of CDG. My role in the company was to design and build websites for our SME clients using WordPress. I also took a lead role in streamlining the design/development process for the 'affordable' website offering.

### CDG, Sunningdale - Graduate Designer MAY 2017 - APR 2018

After graduating I joined CDG as a graduate designer. My role expanded to running client meetings, preparing and conducting focus groups and user testing. As well as working on client projects, I also got the opportunity to work within product teams, creating and refining digital products using agile.

# CDG, Sunningdale - Digital Design Intern MAY 2016 - APR 2017

During my last year at university I got the opportunity to work alongside my study. It allowed me to develop my design and problem solving skills and gain new experience creating design mock-ups and prototypes for clients.

### REFRENCES

#### **BETTINA NISSEN**

University of Edinburgh bettina.nissen@ed.co.uk

#### SALLY HANSON

CDG

sally@shml.co.uk

# **EDUCATION**

SEP 2018 - AUG 2019

University of Edinburgh - MA Design Informatics

Predicted Grade: Merit

SEP 2014 - MAY 2017

University of Winchester - BA Digital Media Design

Grade: First